菲比，快看窗边 那个男的，哇
Phoebe. Will you check out that guy by the window. Wow!
后面那个家伙吗？他真的好矮 而且我想他在自言自语
That guy back there? He's awfully short. And I think he's talking to himself.
老实说 他的床上功夫不怎么样
And to be completely honest,he's not that good in bed.
真的吗？
Really?
我最近是怎么了？ 我对我看到的每个男人心动
What is wrong with me lately? It's like,every guy I see.
譬如说那个男的
I mean,look at that guy,for example.
他不是我喜欢的那一型
That's not someone I would be attracted to.
但现在我觉得…
But right now,with the way I'm feeling..
我想撕开他的运动裤跟搞笑腰包
all I want to do is rip off his sweatpants and fanny pack.
等一下 你怀孕大概四个月了吧？
Wait a second! This is about the fourth month of your pregnancy,right?
-对 -这真的很正常
-Yeah. -This is completely normal.
怀孕四个月时 你的荷尔蒙会很混乱
Around the fourth month,your hormones start going crazy.
-真的吗？你也会这样？ -没错
-Really? So this has happened to you? -Absolutely!
记住我怀的是三胞胎
And keep in mind now,I was carrying triplets.
在医学上来说 我的症状要强上三倍
So in medical terms,I was thrice as randy.
原来是这么一回事
Wow,this explains so much!
上周末我走遍每一家店 坐在圣诞老人的膝盖上
Last weekend,I went from store to store,sitting on Santas' laps.
对，我记得我想要从富乐客（美国最大的运动鞋连锁店）
Yeah,I remember trying to steal a cardboard cutout..
偷走伊万德・霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
of Evander Holyfield from a Foot Locker.
明天我得去看医生 我会问问她的
Well,I go see my doctor tomorrow. I'll ask her about this.
或许她可以 开个药给我吃
Maybe she can give me a pill or something.
对，那正是你需要的东西 你需要吃药
Yeah,that's what you need. A good pill.
不，那个矮疯子认得我 他是我一生中最糟糕的错误
Oh,no. Short,crazy guy recognizes me. Worst mistake of my life.
打电话给我
Call me.
本集播出：缓慢的假期卡片
The.One.With.The.Creepy.Holiday.Card
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
我把我们到洛克菲勒中心的照片 洗出来了
I got our pictures developed from Rockefeller Center.
太棒了，乔伊 你想看我跟蒙娜去溜冰的照片吗？
Great. Hey,Joey,want to check out pictures of me and Mona ice-skating?
通常我会想看 但现在我真的好忙
Ordinarily,I would love to,but I am just swamped right now.
那个怪咸酥饼小贩 帮我们合拍的照片在哪里？
Where are the pictures that that creepy pretzel vendor took of us together?
对 或许在最后面
Oh,yeah. Probably at the end.
天啊，他只拍了我的胸部
Oh,my God! All he took were pictures of my breasts.
我想看看照片
I'm missing picture time!
你知道，她有脸的，罗斯
You know,she has a face,Ross.
这些照片不是我拍的，好吗？
I didn't take these,okay?
我甚至不知道我的相机能放大影像
I didn't even know my camera had a zoom lens.
“知道了，警官”
"Comma,officer."
我们这张合照很不错
-Okay,here's a good one of us.
那张真的很棒
-Wow,that is a good one!
看起来很像节日贺卡，中间有树 还有溜冰客跟雪
It looks like a holiday card.With the tree in the middle and the skaters and the snow.
做的好，卖咸酥饼的变态
Good job,pretzel pervert.
每年我都说我会寄贺卡 但我从来没有那么做
Every year,I say I'm gonna send out holiday cards and I never do it.
你要跟我一起 寄出这张卡片吗？
Do you want to send this one out together?
一起寄我们的合照给大家？
Together? Like,to people?
对，“佳节愉快，蒙娜跟罗斯上” 那一定会很棒，好吗？
Yeah. "Happy holidays,from Mona and Ross." It'll be cute,okay?
好吧
Okay.
-我得去上班了，待会打电话给我？ -没问题
-I gotta get to work. Call me later? -Sure,sure.
-大家再见 -再见
-Bye,guys. -Bye.
恭喜，你刚刚结婚了
Congratulations! You just got married!
我知道，你相信吗？
I know. Can you believe that?
抱歉 一张贺卡有什么大不了的？
I'm sorry. What's the big deal about a holiday card?
已婚夫妻跟家人 才会一起寄照片
Married couples send out cards. Families send out cards.
约会了几个月的情侣 不会一起寄卡片
People who have been dating for a couple of months don't send out cards.
-她疯了吗？ -你说的人是你的太太
-What is she,crazy? -That's your wife you're talking about!
不，我是说真的 那会是一大步
No,really. I mean,that would be like a huge step forward.
我喜欢我们现在的样子
I like things just the way they are.
我终于有一场 不会进展的太快的恋爱
I'm finally in a relationship that's not moving too fast.
一般来说 现在我早该离婚了
You know,ordinarily,I'd be divorced by now.
好吧，告诉她你不想寄卡片 她会怎么做？
Okay,so just tell her you don't wanna send out the card. What's she gonna do?
像这样
This.
好吧 我无意对你施压…
Oh,okay. I didn't mean to put pressure on you..
我只是觉得 跟你一起做这件事会很有趣…
I just thought it would be something fun for us to do together..
但没关系
but okay,that's okay.
好了，别说了，你说的对 那没什么大不了的，我会寄卡片
Okay,stop. Stop. You're right,it's not that big a deal. I'll do the card.
-什么？我说我会做 -我知道，那只是…
-What? I said I'd do it. -I know,it's just..
能给我20块吗？
Can I have $20?
-嗨，准备好吃午餐了吗？ -等一下
-Hi. You ready for lunch? -One second.
-那真可爱 -宾，宾太太
-That's cute. -Bing! And the Bingette!
我就觉得 今天的办公室很热
I thought it felt a little hotter in the office today.
-老婆，你记得我老板道格 -对，嗨
-Oh,honey,you remember my boss,Doug. -Yes. Hi.
好消息，我已经离婚了 我今天早上签了文件
Good news! The divorce is final. I signed the papers this a.m.
我不知道你跟卡拉离婚了 我很遗憾
I didn't know you and Kara divorced. I'm sorry.
遗憾？我终于 可以离开那个苦牢了
Sorry? I finally chewed my leg out of that bear trap.
-恭喜你们 -我们没有离婚
-Congratulations to you guys,though. -No leg-chewing for us,sir.
等着瞧吧
Well,give it time.
我们要庆祝 离婚跟结婚
So the divorce,the marriage,we got a lot to celebrate.
我们明晚 何不一起吃晚餐？
How about we all go out to dinner tomorrow night.
我想不出来 我们要做什么事
I can't think of anything we're doing.
为什么我想不出来 我们要做什么事？
Why can't I think of anything we're doing?
那么就说定明晚了 我六点可以离开法庭
Tomorrow night it is. I should be out of court by 6.
他们一直 把性骚扰案丢给我…
They keep throwing sexual harassment cases at me..
我一直 把他们打得毫无退路
and I keep knocking them out of the park!
好吧，明天见
Okay,see you tomorrow.
你知道的 我们明天不能跟他见面
Just so you know,we're not seeing him tomorrow.
亲爱的，你认识他后 会知道他真的很可怕
Honey,once you get to know him,he's much,much worse.
我没办法一个人去
I can't do this alone.
我很抱歉，我帮不了你 我没办法再跟他共度一个夜晚
Honey,I'm sorry. I can't help you. I can't spend another evening with that man.
你记得他在我们的婚礼上 做了什么吗？
Do you remember how he behaved at our wedding?
那是因为我们没有邀请他
That's because he wasn't invited.
因为他在我们的订婚派对上 为非作歹
Because of the way he behaved at our engagement party.
对，他小便时 直接喷中了冰雕，对吧？
Oh,yeah! Urine cuts right through an ice sculpture,doesn't it?
好吧 就给“B+”好了
Oh,what the hell? B plus.
我去过冲印店了 你看
Hi! I went by the photo shop. Take a look.
这是卡片的初稿 你觉得呢？
Here is a mockup of our card. What do you think?
那真的很棒
Wow,that's great.
你觉得我们该写上 “爱你们的罗斯跟蒙娜”吗？
Do you think it should say,"Love,Ross and Mona"?
我们还没有 对彼此那么说…
Well,we haven't said that to each other yet..
但我猜跟其他人那么说 应该没关系
but I guess it's okay to say it to other people.
-你要多少张？我要一百张 -一百张？
-How many did you want? I'll get 100. -A hundred?
我猜我要…
Well,I guess I'll take..
蒙娜
Mona?
我不确定 印卡片这件事对不对
I'm not sure about the whole card thing.
真的吗？为什么？
Really? Why not?
我们一起寄贺卡？
Sending out a holiday card together?
我不知道我们是不是 到了那个地步
I just don't know if we're really quite there yet.
我没想到那一点 你说的对
I didn't think of it that way. You're right.
-我能问你一个问题吗？ -好啊
-So can I ask you a question? -Yeah.
我们到了哪个地步？
Where are we?
我们到了哪个地步？ 这段关系会有什么结局？
You know,where are we? Where is this relationship going?
我喜欢跟你在一起 我只是希望我们往前走
I love spending time with you. I just hope we're moving forward.
我们该谈一谈 你不觉得吗？
We should talk about that,don't you think?
我们一起印卡片吧
Let's do the card!
-什么？ -卡片，我想我们到了那个地步
-What? -The card! I think we're there!
好吧，但我还是觉得 我们应该谈一谈
Okay. But I still think we should have this conversation.
真的吗？
Really?
即使我们印了卡片？
Even with the card?
朗医生今天没办法过来 辛夫医生会帮你检查
Just so you know,Dr. Long can't be here today,so Dr. Schiff will be seeing you.
好吧 我能问你一个问题吗？
Oh,okay. Can I ask you a question?
是我有问题 还是帮我抽血的那个家伙真的很帅？
Was it me,or was the guy who took my blood sample really cute?
你知道我在说谁吗？ 那个马桶盖头，手指都是毛的家伙
You know who I'm talking about? Bowl haircut,hairy fingers?
事实上别理我 我已经回答了我的问题
Actually,never mind. I just answered my own question.
-瑞秋吗？我是辛夫医生 -没错
-Hi,Rachel? I'm Dr. Schiff. -Yes,you are.
-他真的很帅吧？ -天啊，对
-Okay,now he's cute,right? -Oh,God,yes.
情况如何？
So,how's it going?
真的很不错 但别谈我了
It's going really good. But enough about me! Come on.
你是哪里人？ 你是做哪一行的？
Where are you from? What do you do?
-我是医生 -对，我是指…
-I'm a doctor. -Right. I meant..
你有空的时候 你会煮饭或滑雪吗？
in your spare time. Do you cook? So you ski?
或你会跟太太 还是女朋友一起出去玩？
Or just hang out with your wife,or girlfriend?
我没有太太或女朋友 但我很喜欢滑雪
I don't have a wife or a girlfriend,but I do like to ski.
我喜欢滑雪 那真的很神奇吧？
I love to ski! How amazing is this?
-你觉得不舒服吗？ -不，我非常舒服
-Are you experiencing any discomfort? -No,I'm very comfortable.
-放屁会不舒服吗？ -不会
-Any painful gas? -No!
辛夫医生 那是哪门子的问题？
Dr. Schiff! What kind of question is that?
好吧 麻烦你躺下来
Okay,then. Would you like to lie down on the table?
你要我躺下吗？
Would you like me to lie down on the table?
-这是怎么一回事？ -你也感觉到了吗？
-Is there something going on here? -Do you feel it too?
-嗨 -门诊看得如何？
-Hi. -How did your doctor's appointment go?
让我想一想，今天他们派了 一个“帅哥”医生给我
Well,let's see,they gave me "cute boy" doctor today.
检查到一半 我用手指指着他下巴的酒窝
In the middle of the exam,I put my pinkie in his chin dimple.
-天啊 -你为什么要那么做？
-Oh,my God! -Why did you do that?
还记得我怀孕四个月时 出的那个小问题吗？
Remember that little problem I was having during my fourth month of pregnancy?
对 伊万德・霍利菲尔德的人形立牌
Oh,yeah! The Evander Holyfield phase.
天啊，你真的很难受 你甚至来找我
Oh,man! You were so hard up,you practically came on to me.
少做梦了
You wish.
如果我真的要你 我可以把上你
Hey,I could have had you if I wanted you.
是吗？来试试看吧
Oh,yeah? Come and get it.
好了，连这段对话都能挑起我的欲望 我真的有问题
Okay,even this is turning me on. You guys,I got problems.
罗斯 你跟蒙娜还好吧？
Oh,hey. Hey,Ross! How's it going with you and Mona?
你们还在一起吗？
Are you guys still together?
对，我们有所进展 你们会接到我们的卡片
Yeah,we're moving forward. You'll be getting our card.
你们要一起寄贺卡？
You're doing a holiday card?
我们不只要寄贺卡 她还要谈一谈…
We're not just doing a card. She also wants to have the conversation..
我们的交往 会有什么结局
about where the relationship is going.
女人
Women!
我知道 为什么你们需要谈一谈
I know! Why do you guys need to have this conversation?
懂得自我尊重的男人不会问女人 “我们会有什么结局？”
No self-respecting man would ask a woman,"So where is this going?"
罗斯，你问过我
Ross,you asked me that.
你像是本没打开的书，好吗？ 我不会读心术
You were a closed book,okay? I'm not a mind reader!
你要跟她说什么？ 你们会有什么结局？
What are you gonna say to her? Where is this relationship going?
我不知道，我真的喜欢她 我想跟她继续约会
I don't know. I really like her and I wanna keep dating her.
-告诉她 -我不能
-So tell her that. -No,I can't.
因为她会说 我们不会有结局…
Because then she's gonna say,"Well,it's not moving anywhere..
-我们应该分手 -没错
-then we should just break up." -Yeah,that's true.
而且我讨厌谈那些事 我真的不太会应付那些事
Besides,I hate those conversations. I'm horrible at them. Really.
或许我需要暗示她…
Maybe I need some kind of a gesture..
我们的确有进展 不必去谈这件事
something that says we're moving forward without having to talk about it.
像是请她 搬去跟你一起住？
Like asking her to move in with you?
比那个小
Smaller than that.
-帮她录录音带？ -比那个大
-Making her a mix tape? -Bigger than that.
-给她你家的钥匙 -我们比较接近录录音带
-Give her a key to your apartment. -We were closer with the mix tape.
你说过“我爱你”吗？ 你可以说“我爱你”
Have you said,"I love you"? You could say,"I love you."
我想我还没有到那个地步
I don't think I'm quite there yet.
但我可以说 “我爱跟你在一起”
But I could say,"I love spending time with you."
-我们讨厌那句话 -那像是被人打了一巴掌
-We hate that. -That is a slap in the face.
算了，你们知道吗？ 我会跟她谈
Forget it. You know what? I'll just have the conversation.
我会说我喜欢我们现在的样子 并怀着最好的期待
I'll just say I like things the way they are,and hope for the best.
你觉得呢？瑞秋
What do you think,Rach?
我想 如果这里冷一点…
I think if it was a little colder in here..
我可以看到 你的乳头硬起来
I could see your nipples through that sweater.
宾？我们今晚八点出发
Bing? We're all set for tonight,8:00.
我们没办法去 莫妮卡得上班
As it turns out,we can't do it. Monica has to work.
我前妻不上班
My ex-wife didn't work.
除非你说 回娘家是“上班”
Unless you call turning into her mother "work."
好吧，那么明天晚上
Fine. Tomorrow night then.
-她明晚也不能来 -为什么？
-Tomorrow's no good for her,either. -Why not?
她的草地保龄球巡回赛
It's the semifinals..
要打准决赛
of her bocce ball tournament.
好吧，那么后天晚上
Okay. The night after that then.
那是决赛的日子 我想她应该会赢
Well,that's the finals,and I think she's gonna go all the way,sir.
发生了什么事？宾 你老婆不喜欢我吗？
What's going on,Bing? Does your wife have a problem with me or something?
你说的太夸张了
Well,now you're just talking crazy.
我们三个 为什么不能一起出去？
Then why can't the three of us go out together?
因为我们分居了
Because we split up.
莫妮卡跟我分居了
Monica and I split up.
抱着我
Hold me.
天啊，宾 我不能说我很讶异
Good God,Bing. Well,I can't say I'm altogether surprised.
我看到她看你的眼神 就知道她不爱你
I saw the way she looked at you,and there was no love there.
她看着我时 充满了欲望
And the way she looked at me,pure lust.
在这种时候 只有掐人才能让我泄愤
What would really help me through this tough time is choking someone.
我了解你的感觉
I know how you feel. Oh,yeah.
我知道 将你的爱给了一个女人…
I know what it's like to give a woman all your love..
结果被她 反打一巴掌的感觉
and then have that love thrown back in your face.
法庭还判定 你得到那对左撇子胖双胞胎的监护权
And then the court decides to give you custody of those fat,left-handed twins.
他们很幸运还有你
Well,they're lucky to have you,sir.
宾，孩子 我们得让你忘了这件事
Bing,my boy,we're gonna get you over this.
我有个计划，拿着你的外套 我们去脱衣舞俱乐部
Here's the plan: Grab your coat,we're going to a strip club!
不 莫妮卡会生气的
Oh,no! Monica would freak.
但谁管那个臭女人呢
But to hell with that bitch!
咖啡来了
Here we go.
蒙娜，我们该来谈谈 我们之间了
Mona,it's time we had a conversation about where things are with us.
我想那是我提出的建议
Yeah,I think I suggested that.
我们非常….
We are so..
我真的很喜欢你 我喜欢跟你在一起
Well,I really like you. And I love hanging out with you.
我非常开心
And I'm having a lot of fun.
好吧
Okay.
如果只是为了好玩 我们就不必交往了
There's no point in spending time with someone if it's just fun.
我们得有结果，对吧？
It's gotta be going somewhere,right?
我们会有什么结果？
So where is it going?
那真是个问题
That's the real question.
答案是…
And the answer is..
我们会…
it's going somewhere..
很好玩
fun.
我知道你在想什么 10年前你只想玩玩
I know what you're thinking. Fun was fine for you 10 years ago.
但现在你不年轻了
But you're not getting any younger.
我不是说你 不是你
No! I mean,not you. Not you.
你越来越年轻了
You are getting younger!
你每一秒都在变年轻 你有什么秘诀？
You're getting younger by the second. What's your secret?
抱歉，我们是什么关系？
I'm sorry,so where are we?
总而言之…
Well,to sum up..
我们很开心 你看起来很年轻
we're having fun. You look young.
-好吧… -但那是不够的
-Okay.. -But that's not enough.
所以…
So..
这是我家的钥匙
here's a key to my apartment.
-真的吗？ -真的
-Really? -Really.
你不觉得太快了吗？
You don't think this is too fast?
你给她 你家的钥匙？
You gave her a key to your apartment?
不只是那样 我给了她我唯一的钥匙
Not just a key. I gave her the only key!
现在我是个恋爱失败 无家可归的家伙
I am now a homeless person in a very serious relationship!
-你为什么要给她钥匙？ -是她逼我的，好吗？
-Why did you give her a key? -She talked me into a corner,okay?
她就像个谈话魔法师
She's like this conversational wizard.
你被逼着 跟她谈…
So you had the conversation you didn't wanna have..
给了她 你不想做的承诺
and you made the gesture you didn't wanna make.
我一开始说“嗨 今天我做了一件很棒的事”吗？
Did I start this by saying,"Hey,I did something awesome today"?
-你们有我家的钥匙吗？ -你根本没给我们
-Do either of you have a key to my place? -I don't think you've ever given us keys.
我为什么要那么做？那是我家
Yeah,why would I? It's my home.
-罗斯，你们谈的如何？ -很棒，现在我流落街头
-Ross,how did the conversation go? -Great. I live on the street.
哪里？
Where?
-嗨 -好吧，莫妮卡，瑞秋…
-Hi. -Okay,Monica,Rachel..
-他是我朋友罗杰 -嗨，罗杰
-this is my friend Roger. -Hi,Roger.
我去拿饮料 你能帮我吗？
I'll get us some drinks. Could you help me?
好吧
Yeah,okay.
他是来跟你做爱的
He's here to have sex with you.
-什么？ -别客气
-What? -You're welcome.
-菲比，不 -没关系，他是个处男
-Phoebe,no! -It's okay. He's a virgin.
瑞秋，我跟这个家伙提过 我想他会跟你做爱
Rachel,I was talking to this guy. I think he'll have sex with you.
让他们两个独处一下吧
Let's leave these two alone.
不，我不在乎我的荷尔蒙在做什么 我不会随便跟男人上床
No! I don't care what my hormones are doing! I won't do it with some random guy!
好吧，那么你去告诉罗杰 因为他真的很期待
Fine! Then you tell Roger,because he was really looking forward to this!
宾，看看那对双胞胎姐妹 一起跳舞
Bing! Look at those twin sisters dancing together.
我出钱请她们 坐在你大腿上跳舞
Let me buy you a lap dance with those girls.
很好，而且只有一个女孩在跳舞
That's all right,sir. And that's just one girl.
-宾，这是什么？ -那是我的手
-Bing,what's this? -It's a hand.
你把它当成拿鸡尾酒的工具了
It's a thing you use as a Jack and Coke holder.
那是婚戒，把它丢了 我们把它丢到东河去
It's a wedding ring. Get rid of it. We'll throw it in the East River!
-不 -要
-No! -Yes!
我那么做了，那让我觉得好多了 你甚至可能会打中海鸥
I did it,and I felt a lot better! You might even hit a seagull in the head.
好吧 我需要一堆备用钥匙
Okay. I'm gonna need a bunch of extra keys.
很明显地 我会毫无理由地将它们送人
Apparently,I give them away for no reason at all.
罗斯，发生了什么事？ 你在换锁？
Ross,what's going on? You're changing the lock?
不
No.
是那个家伙在换锁
That guy is.
你把你家的钥匙给我 然后你换了锁？
You give me a key to your apartment,and then you change the lock?
祝你好运
Good luck,buddy.
我以为我们往前迈进了一步 你给我完全混乱的讯息
I thought we were moving forward. Now you're sending me all these mixed signals.
你到底想告诉我什么？
What are you trying to tell me?
我想告诉你…
I'm trying to tell you..
我帮你录了一卷录音带
I made you a mix tape.
-什么？ -我爱你
-What? -I love you.
我爱跟你在一起
And I love spending time with you.
-亲爱的，我回来了 -你从龙舌兰酒工厂回来？
-Hi,honey,I'm home. -From the tequila factory?
那真的好可怕
It was awful.
为了逃避跟道格的晚餐约会 我告诉他你跟我分居了
To get out of going to dinner with Doug,I told him you and I split up.
他拖我去脱衣舞俱乐部 还有色情酒吧
So then he took me to these strip clubs and sleazy bars.
我不肯把婚戒交给他 他用汽水罐丢小鸟
When I wouldn't give him my wedding ring,he threw a soda can at a bird.
过来 我可以用嘴巴呼吸
Come here. I can breathe through my mouth.
-亲爱的 -你知道最糟糕的是什么吗？
-Oh,sweetie. -You know what the worst part was?
我可以看到 没有你的生活
I got to see what my life would be like without you.
那像是有贴身舞的《美好人生》（又译《风云人物》）
It was like It's a Wonderful Life with lap dances.
请答应我 你永远不会离开我…
Please promise me that you'll never leave me..
我们会一起变老 相伴一生
that we'll grow old together,and be with each other for the rest of our lives.
我答应你
I promise.
说到相伴一生 我们今年一起寄贺卡吧
Speaking of together,how about we send out a holiday card this year?
我不知道我们是不是到了那个地步
I don't know if we're there yet.
我想订披萨 我能问你一个问题吗？
I'd like to order a pizza. Can I ask you a question?
今晚是那个金发帅哥外送吗？ 非常“阿贝克隆比&费奇”（年轻人休闲服饰第一品牌）
Is the cute blond guy delivering tonight? Very "Abercrombie & Fitch."
-我再打给你 -你在跟谁讲电话？
-I'll call you back. -Who was that?
-我在订披萨 -你挂掉订披萨的电话？
-It's just the pizza place. -You hung up on the pizza place?
我不会挂掉你朋友打来的电话
I don't hang up on your friends.
-抱歉，今天我很不好受 -怎么了？
-Sorry,honey,I'm just having a rough day. -What's wrong?
-你不会想听的 -不然我为什么要问？
-You don't want to hear about it. -Then why did I ask?
这真的很丢脸 但最近自从我怀孕后…
Okay,this is really embarrassing,but lately,with this whole pregnancy thing..
我发现自己…
I'm just finding myself..
我该怎么说呢？
How do I put this?
春情大发
Erotically charged.
那是“好色”的学名吗？
Is that college talk for "horny"?
对，我有那样的感觉 不知道该怎么办
Yeah. I have all of these feelings,and I don't know what to do about them.
我没办法像正常人去约会 没关系，因为我不需要男朋友
I can't date like a normal person,which is fine because I don't need a relationship.
我只要一夜情 我只要性
All I really want is one great night! Just sex.
没有牵绊 没有责任
No strings attached. No relationship.
跟我喜欢的人在一起 他得知道他在做什么
With someone I feel comfortable with,and who knows what he's doing.
只要疯狂度过一夜 那真的那么难…
For just one great night. I mean,is that really so hard..
找到吗？
to find?
你今天过得如何？
So how was your day?
很好，我看见一只大鸽子
Good. I saw a pretty big pigeon.
我还得早起 快七点了
Well,I gotta get up early,and it's almost 7:00.
-我得回房了 -晚安
-I gotta go to my room. -Good night!
晚安
Good night!
-我不能那么做 -我没有要你那么做
-I can't do it! -I didn't ask you to do it!
-你是瑞秋 -你是乔伊
-You're Rachel! -You're Joey!
-你是我的朋友 -你也是我的朋友
-You're my friend! -Right back at you.
对，而且那是不对的 那既奇怪又糟糕
Yeah. Plus,it would be wrong,and weird and bad!
太糟糕了，但我不知道你在说什么 我没有要求你做什么事
So bad! But I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't ask you to do anything!
我知道
I know!
-你想做吗？ -不
-You wanna do it? -No!
-我只是在考验你 -那么就这样了
-I'm just testing you! -Well,that's the end of this conversation!
-我们没谈过这件事 -没错
-This conversation never happened! -Never happened!
-晚安 -晚安
-Good night! -Good night!
快回你房里
Get back in there!
听着，关于罗杰的事 我很抱歉
Listen,I'm sorry about that whole thing with Roger.
那真的是不对的 我想弥补你
It really wasn't right. And I want to make it up to you.
我带了一样 我觉得你会喜欢的东西来
So I brought you something I think you'll really enjoy.
伊万德・霍利菲尔德
Evander Holyfield
我只是借给你用，好吗？ 我会把它拿回去的
Now this is just a loan,okay? I'm gonna want him back.
我得走了
I'm gonna go now.
抱歉 我以为我办得到，但我不能
I'm sorry. I thought I could do it,and I can't.